proav.co.uk 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

**Who manages this site?**  
This website is managed by Proactive UK Ltd, Unit 1, Eastman Way, Hemel Hempstead, Herts, HP2 7DU. Telephone 01442 292929.

**Privacy and Cookies**  
Under the terms of the Data Protection Act 1998, we have a legal duty to protect any information we collect from you. We will treat all your Personal Information as confidential (although we reserve the right to disclose this information in the circumstances set out below). We will keep it on a secure server and we will fully comply with all applicable UK Data Protection and consumer legislation from time to time in place.

When you shop on this Website, we will ask you to input, and will collect Personal Information from you such as your name, e-mail address, billing address, delivery address, telephone number, product selections, credit card or other payment information and a password. See further information on credit cards below.

We confirm that any Personal Information which you provide to us (or which is available on public registers) and any User Information from which we can identify you, is held in accordance with the registration we have with the Data Commissioner's Office. We use your information only for the following purposes:

  * Processing your orders
  * To serve website content and advertisements to you
  * To administer this website
  * To contact you about leaving a review on a product once your order has been completed
  * If you consent, to notify you of products or special offers that may be of interest to you
  * You should be aware that if we are requested by the police or any other regulatory or government authority investigating suspected illegal activities to provide your Personal Information and /or User Information, we are entitled do so

When entering any of our contests or prize draws, you provide your name, email address and mailing address. If you win, we will send the prize to the address entered and notify you by email. When you enter a contest or prize draw, you are also included in our newsletter list to receive notice of promotions, specials and new additions to the Website. You may unsubscribe from this news list by following the unsubscribe instructions in any email received.

We use Cookies to keep track of your current shopping session to personalise your experience and so that you may retrieve your shopping basket at any time; if you do not accept Cookies, you will be unable to use this Website for shopping purposes, only for browsing and research.

_**Delivery photography:**_ If one of our Customer Delivery Partners attempts to deliver an order to your address and finds there's no-one available to receive it, we reserve the right to take a photograph of the outside of the property to assure you we were in the right geographical location to fulfil your order, and confirm we had located the correct address. We can assure you that this photograph won't be published or circulated, or used for any other purpose other than verification, and that it's held securely in compliance with Data Protection legislation.

**Can cookies threaten users' privacy?**  
Cookies are stored on the computer's hard drive. They cannot access the hard drive - so a cookie cannot read other information saved on the hard drive, or get a user's e-mail address etc. They only contain and transfer to the server as much information as the users themselves have disclosed to a certain web site. Cookies are not able to access any of your payment information, telephone numbers etc. Proav does not use cookies to gather any personal information. For any further information on cookies please see www.aboutcookies.org.

**Credit Card Information / Finance Applications**  
We do not store any credit card details or any other sensitive information that may be required to complete an online finance application. All credit card transactions are processed by Barclaycard who use PCI compliant software, and the highest level of encryption to ensure that your credit card details are kept secure at all times. All finance application are processed by Barclays Partner Finance for personal consumer loans or an FCA approved loan provider for Business loans. Additionally our website is secured by THAWTE encryption during the transfer from our website to the Barclaycard card processing website, the Barclays Partner Finance website or the FCA approved Business Loan provider. It is at these sites where you will be asked to enter your card and / or personal details. The THAWTE certificate is only awarded to websites such as [www.proav.co.uk](http://www.proav.co.uk/) that pass THAWTE’s own rigorous PCI compliance procedures and ongoing monitoring programmes. The certificate may be viewed by clicking on the padlock at the bottom of the payment pages.

**Linking To Other Sites**  
The proav.co.uk site is one of several owned by Proactive UK Ltd and contains links to other Proactive UK Ltd websites. The information described in "What information do we collect?" may be passed to these websites. This site also contains links to other sites. Proactive UK Ltd is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

**Advertisers**  
We use outside advertising companies to display advertisements on our site. These advertisements may contain cookies. Cookies received with banner advertisements are collected by the advertising company, and we do NOT have access to this information.

**Public Forums**  
This site may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Right To Request Information**  
You have a right to request a copy of any personal information held by us at any time, in order to check its accuracy. If you wish to do this, please write to:

Data Protection Officer  
Proactive UK Ltd  
1 Eastman Way,  
Hemel Hempstead,  
Herts,  
HP2 7DU,  
United Kingdom
